[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Kyle：在休息之前，我们讨论了将承诺链接在一起。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Before the break we talked about chaining promises together.
但是这种方法从根本上是有限制的。
But there's something fundamentally limiting about this approach.
这种方法的基本限制是您必须了解所有
The fundamental limitation of this approach is that you have to know all of
提前承诺。
the promises in advance.
你必须知道在你的流量控制中有多少个步骤。
You have to know how many steps are in your flow control.
有时，甚至在大多数情况下，情况就是这样。
Sometimes, and maybe even most of the time, that is going to be the case.
你会知道，有一套离散的步骤你可以安排。
You're going to know, there's a discrete set of steps that you can lay out.
你可以把你的承诺连在一起
And you can chain your promises together to
近似于任何必要的流量控制。
approximate whatever flow control is necessary.
但在某些情况下，这并不是真的。
But there will be cases where that won't be true.
在某些情况下，无法预测作者的时间，
There will be cases where it's impossible to predict author time,
可能有三个步骤，五个步骤，还是一千个步骤。
whether there might be three steps or five steps or a thousand steps.
你可能不想重复这个模式上千次。
And you probably don't wanna repeat this pattern thousand times over.
这需要大量的复制和粘贴，可能会出现很多错误，
That's a lot of copy and pasting, a lot of mistakes can be made,
很多更新，如果你必须调整一些东西。
a lot of updates if you have to tweak something.
因此，练习四将要求我们
So, exercise four is going to ask us to
改变我们大脑思考它的方式，至少一点点。
change the way our brains are thinking about it, at least a little bit.
试图了解我们可能如何使用承诺的功能性本质。
To try to understand how we might use the functional nature of promises.
他们一起工作的方式，他们的作曲方式。
The way that they work together, the way that they compose.
我们如何才能以这样一种方式使用它，我们可以得到我们的。
How might we use that in such a fashion that we can get our.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：将我们的流控制设置为任意长度，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Get our flow control to be an arbitrary length,
这就是我想说的。
is what I'm trying to say.
我们怎样才能让它达到一个任意的长度，这样就可以有一个步骤，
How can we get it to an arbitrary length so that there could be one step,
三步，还是一百步？
three steps, or 100 steps?
所以，我们要去打开练习四。
So, we're gonna go and open up exercise four.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：我已经给了你GET文件，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: I've already given you the get file,
因为我们已经实现了这一部分。
cuz we've already implemented that part.
但我现在要你做的是我想让你想想，我可能是什么工具
But what I want you to do now is I want you to think, what tools might I be
能够使用创建
able to use to create
一个可以任意长的列表，并且仍然有所有这些动作发生？
a list that could be arbitrarily long, and still have all these actions occur?
我很努力地给你提示，但没有给你完整的解决方案。
I'm trying very hard to give you hints without giving you the full solution.
如果你还记得的话，我们在另一个研讨会上谈到了效用。
So if you recall, we talked about utility in a different workshop.
我们谈到了像地图这样的公用事业，
We talked about utilities like map,
它可以获取一系列值并对其进行转换。
which can take a list of values and transform it.
我们讨论了一个叫做Reduce的实用程序，
And we talked about a utility called reduce,
它可以获取一系列值并将它们组合在一起。
which can take a list of values and compose them together.
所以如果我有一个URL列表。
So if I had a list of URLs.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：我可以将URL列表转换成什么？
&gt;&gt; Kyle: What could I transform that list of URLs into?
也许我可以将URL列表转换为承诺列表。
Maybe I could transform that list of URLs into a list of promises.
如果我有一张承诺的清单，我该如何将所有这些承诺组合在一起呢？
And if I had a list of promises, how might I compose all those promises together?
我也许可以减少一些承诺
I could maybe do a reduction on the list of promises and
创建一个任意长的承诺链。
create an arbitrarily long promise chain.
这是你的练习四。
That's your exercise four.
玩得开心。
Have fun.